

CONTACT

+358 0449239180

https://www.linkedin.com/in/th araka-ranathunga-58ba52205/

https://github.com/TharakaRana thunga

💡 Kivikatu 5 B 51, 15700, Lahti

SKILLS

Microsoft Office

Team Player

Public Relations

Time Management

Leadership

Effective Communication

Critical Thinking

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Sinhala (Mother tongue)

English (Fluent)

Chinese (Good)

Japanese (Good)

Finnish (Basic)

TKT CLILL - Band 4

PTE - 78

HSK Level 4

JLPT Level 3

CERTIFICATES

Hygiene Passport

THARAKA RANATHUNGA

PROFILE

I am a highly motivated professional with a proven track, a strong team player who thrives on collaboration, and a committed learner who takes up challenges. I am also a hard worker who always tries to complete the responsibilities taking the optimum output in providing the industry with the best production with knowledge, expertise and research.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CLEANER (PART-TIME) INHOUSE PARTNERS OY, LAHTI

01/11/2024 - Present Lahti

• Cleaning supermarket premises

ADVERTISEMENT DISTRIBUTOR (PART-TIME) SSM OY

28/08/2024 - Present Lahti

• Sorting and delivering advertisements

LECTURER - SABARAGAMUWA UNIVERSITY OF SRI LANKA

03/05/2020 - 30/06/2024 Belihuloya, Sri Lanka

- Teaching Mandarin Chinese and Japanese to undergraduates
- Curriculum designing, assessing and evaluating students' works
- Organizing and conducting workshops, field tours, conferences and examinations
- Taking minutes of meetings, recording and reporting

INSTRUCTOR - SRI LANKA INTERNATIONAL BUDDHIST ACADEMY

15/01/2018 - 30/04/2020 Colombo, Sri Lanka

- Designing course content
- Teaching Chinese and English language to undergraduates and diploma students, assessing and evaluating students' works
- Conducting meetings, workshops and events

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING IN INDUSTRIAL INFORMATION
TECHNOLOGY-LAB UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES, LAHTI, FINLAND
15/08/2024 - PRESENT

CONTENT AND LANGUAGE INTEGRATED LEARNING - AUSTRALIAN COLLEGE OF BUSINESS AND TECHNOLOGY

MASTER OF ARTS IN LINGUISTICS - UNIVERSITY OF KELANIYA, SRI LANKA 19/04/2019-01/05/2023

BACHELOR OF ARTS - SABARAGAMUWA UNIVERSITY OF SRI LANKA 16/07/2013 - 10/11/2017

CERTIFICATE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE - NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF BUSINESS MNAGEMENT, SRI LANKA

DIPLOMA IN AIRLINE TICKETING - INTERNATIONAL AIRLINE TICKETING ACADEMY, SRI LANKA